

Personal

Name:

Maksym Sazhko

Address:

Ukraine 65114 Odessa

Date of birth:

09-07-1993

Place of birth:

Odessa

Gender:

Male

Nationality:

Ukrainian

Marital status:

married

Links:

Github Linkedin <u>telegram</u>

Email:

maksymsazhko@gmail.com

Phone number:

+3809392249**

Languages:

English Ukrainian

Maksym Sazhko

Experienced and self-motivated Electrical Engineer with five+ years of industry experience on different ships (1974-2013 dates of built), looking for new opportunities in any country (shore/offshore/sea), and on any equipment. Have skills in engineering(developing) of drafts, due to my first degree and first job (ACAD, Revit). Creative and quick studying person with great communication skills, erudite and have great experience with solving extraordinary problems.

Work experience

Electrical Technical Officer

Oct 2016 - Feb 2022

VShips

Grown up from trainee to officer. Had 7 contracts - 3 was as trainee, and 4 was as officer. Every contract was perfect- great characteristic and reviews. Had 1 year break for finishing degree before becoming an officer.

Hydrotechnical Engineer

Aug 2014 - Jul 2016

Private company, Odessa

Start working as an engineer during my 4th grade at university. Was making drafts, calculations of structures, general plans. After degree, started to communicate with customer, had several business trips.

Education

Hydrotechnical Engineering

Aug 2010 - Aug 2015

Odessa National Marine University, Odessa

Exploitation of Ship Electrical Equipment

Aug 2016 - Aug 2019

Odessa National Maritime College, Odessa

Skills

Communication Skills Microsoft Office Adaptability Fast Learner Circuit Design Critical Thinking Skills

Knowledge of Technical

Diagrams

Courses

Frontend developing

Mar 2022 - Present

ELEKS

- -Git
- -HTML/CSS
- -JavaScript & DOM API
- -React

127.0.0.1:5500/index2.html